JONGGU JAKE BAEK

Full-Stack Web Developer

Phone: 519-330-8892 | Email: jakejonggubaek@gmail.com

LINKS

LinkedIn: https://ca.linkedin.com/in/jake-jonggu-baek-0b153110b

GitHub: https://github.com/jakejonggubaek Portfolio: https://www.jakeisbaek.com

SKILLS

HTML5 CSS3 SASS JavaScript jQuery ReactJS Git
NodeJS Firebase RESTful APIs Java Responsive UI
MySQL Accessibility Team Player Communication

PROFILE

I am a web developer with strong responsive web design skills with other front end background knowledge to build dry, clean, and accessible applications. My passion for problem solving, an eagerness to learn and to adapt new technologies are strengthened by my previous experiences in web development & consulting roles. I am looking forward to applying my results-driven work style along with my collaboration and supportive attitude to your team.

RECENT PROJECTS

Popsipoll (link)

HTML, CSS, SASS, JavaScript, React, Firebase

 A responsive React project that provides create / share / vote polls & poll results with dark / light mode and preview poll functions.

Jake's Travel Survey (<u>link)</u>

HTML, CSS, SASS, JavaScript, React, Firebase

 A responsive React project that provides travel preference survey so that travel agency can collect data of clients' travel preference.

Donno what to cook (link)

HTML, CSS, SASS, JavaScript, RESTful API

 A responsive web application that provides random recipe based on what users have in their fridge.

EDUCATION

Juno College of Technology

Web Development Immersive Bootcamp, 2021

Juno College of Technology

JavaScript Course, 2020

Hanyang University

Urban Engineering B.Sc 2007 - 2013

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Samsung SDS

Junior Web Developer, 2013 - 2015

- Managed main page, sign in, log in/out systems using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Java, SQL in a cross functional team.
- Improved client's (Samsung Fire & Marine Insurance) web application successfully without any issue, and maintained the system by proactively monitoring live logs to ensure quality.
- Experienced many projects through collaborating with different companies in fast-paced environment - applied new security tools, enhanced ally, and launched first mobile application.

OTHER EXPERIENCE

Flight Centre Canada

Travel Consultant, 2018 - 2020

- Achieved 1st tier sales goal with excellent customer service and efficient work habits.
- Contributed to the team's success to achieve the best team sales - providing support, committing to team goals.

*References available upon request.